

Ishita Agarwal Multi Media Journalist

My Contact

✓ Ishitaagarwal039@gmail.com

(8394031238

Business Point, Qila Rampur Road Bareilly

https://ishita-portfolio.netlify.app/

Hard Skill

- · Content Creation
- Podcasting
- Hindi and English Typing
- Reporting
- Animation
- Anchoring

Soft Skill

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Optimistic
- Hardworking

Education Background

- Invertis University
 Bachelor's in Journalism and Mass communication
 Completed in 2022
- Girish Prasad Memorial College Intermediate
 Completed in 2019
- Girish Prasad Memorial College
 High School
 Completed in 2017

About Me

A journalist with a soul that is zealous and candour, along with the intentions to inspire with her work of bringing out breaking news plots. Carrying with her, a prolonged experience in researching and crafting articles that the people find resonant and cognizable, along with not lacking in information that keeps the people compelled. Also, expresses ability to produce innovative ideas to expand readership.

Professional Experience

Dainik Bhaskar | Sub Editor (Sports)

August 2024 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- Works in the National newsroom of print as a sports journalist.
- Cover National and International Sports for print.
- · Write stories and cordinate with state level reporters.

Dainik Bhaskar | Fellowship

August 2023 - July 2024

Key responsibilities:

- Works in Digital newsroom on sports, national & international desk.
- Works as a Video producer for DB Digital.
- Helps in Reporting for Madhya Pradesh local.
- Edit articles written by strings for Bhopal local.

Amar Ujala | Sports, Youth and Lifestyle Reporter

February 2022 - August 2023

Key responsibilities:

- Collect the information about happenings of sports, youth and Lifestyle.
- Choose the correct and authentic piece from a bunch of information and mould it into a news copy.
- Podcasting for Amar Ujala Awaaz.
- Review the news from the rest of other media publications.

RocketTech| Social Media Manager/ Content writer

3 months Internship (2020)

Key responsibilities

- Write the content and arrange it for daily posting.
- Manage a sheet for post engagement, followers, hashtags etc.
- Make a report at the end of the month and plan a strategy for next month to increase engagement.

Achievements

2021- Winner in Advertisement making competition - The Ad-Mad Show

2020-Published in the anthologies like Stardust and A Dreamer's Journal

2022-Performed at Tape a Tale and Unerase Poetry